Comrade-General.
We are close.
You can see.
You can see our progress.
We just need more ti...
You have one year.
Yes, Comrade-General.
♪ Just a little more time
Is all we're asking for ♪
♪ 'Cause just a little more time
Could open closing doors ♪
♪ Just a little uncertainty
Can bring you down ♪
♪ And nobody wants to know you now ♪
- ♪ Nobody wants to show you... ♪
- Mike!
Mike, stop! Stop!
- ♪ So if you're lost and on your own ♪
- Mike! Stop!
Mike! Mike!
- ♪ You can never surrender ♪
- Stop!
- What, you don't like it?
- No!
Don't look at the dogs,
work the lock.
Work the lock. Work the lock.
Don't look at the dogs.
You looked at the dogs.
Sometimes everything goes
exactly as planned.
Hey!
Three-inch minimum!
Leave the door open three inches!
El, open this door.
Open the...
What's wrong?
My God, that was priceless!
Did you see his face?
It was like a tomato!
Yeah, a fat tomato.
- I wish I was still with you.
- I know.
Me too.
But I'll see you tomorrow, all right?
First thing.
Tomorrow.
- You're late.
- Sorry!
- Again.
- We're gonna miss the opening.
Yeah, if you keeping whining
about it. Let's go!
"If you guys keep whining about it.
Nyeh-nyeh-nyeh."
- Just please stop talking, dude.
- Let me guess.
You were busy.
Oh, yeah, real mature, Lucas.
"Oh, El, I wish we could make out forever,
and never hang out
with any of our friends."
Lucas, stop.
- Will thinks it's funny.
- Because it is.
Yeah, it's so funny that I want to spend
romantic time with my girlfriend.
I'm spending romantic time
with my girlfriend.
- Hey!
- Excuse us! Sorry! Sorry!
Sorry, sorry, sorry!
- Excuse me, I'm sorry.
- Sorry.
- Hey!
- Watch it!
Yeah! Watch it, nerd!
Isn't it past your bedtime?
Isn't it time you died?
- Psycho!
- Butthead!
- Mall rat!
- Fart face!
Oh, now that was mature.
Hey, dingus, your children are here.
Again? Seriously?
Come on, come on.
I swear, if anybody hears about this...
We're dead!
All clear.
See, Lucas? We made it.
- We missed the previews.
- Still made it. Fart face.
Shh.
- Skittles.
- Thanks.
- Come on!
The hell?
That's weird.
That isn't gonna work, dingus.
Oh, really?
Let there be light.
Hey.
You okay?
Yeah.
Are you sure?
Of course.
Okay.
Shit!
Shit, shit, shit, shit, shit!
- Wh... What's wrong?
- It's almost 9:00.
- What?
- We forgot to reset the clocks.
- The power went out last night, remember?
- Oh, shit!
Whoa!
♪ Come on with a gun ♪
♪ Come on with a heart attack... ♪
Hey, hey, hey!
- Wait up.
- Oh, no, I'll eat at work.
- I'm late.
- No.
- Your cheek.
- All right, all right.
- I gotta run. See you later.
- All right.
Ugh. Gross.
Well, I don't think you're gonna think
it's gross when you fall in love.
I'm not gonna fall in love.
Okay.
Hey.
What happened here?
I don't know.
♪ Love that was new to you ♪
♪ You open up the door ♪
♪ I fall below my feet ♪
♪ I crawl out on the floor ♪
Can you please drive faster?
Do you wanna break down? We're lucky
this thing still drives at all.
I'm serious, Jonathan, I can't be late.
- You mean we can't be late.
- No, I mean I can't be late.
- They like you no matter what you do.
- Hey, they like you too.
Yeah. They like that I'm
a coffee delivery machine.
They don't actually like me
or respect me
as a living, breathing human
with a brain.
Wait, you just...
you just gotta be patient, okay?
They're set in their ways, you know?
But... once they realize
what a gifted writer you are,
they'll come around.
I really don't need a Jonathan Byers
pep talk right now.
Can you just... please drive faster?
Okay.
This is Gold Leader,
returning to base. Do you copy? Over.
This is Gold Leader, returning to base.
Do you copy? Over.
I repeat: This is Gold Leader,
returning to base. Do you copy? Over.
- I repeat: This is goddamn Gold Leader...
- Dusty!
- What?
- Relax! For goodness' sake.
I'm in range. They should be answering.
You've been away a whole month,
honeybun. Maybe they just...
forgot.
♪ You open up the door ♪
♪ I fall below my feet ♪
♪ I crawl out on the floor... ♪
At least someone's happy I'm home.
It's just a dream.
You're dreaming.
Now!
Cannonball!
♪ We're gonna rock this town ♪
♪ Make 'em scream and shout... ♪
Marco!
Polo!
♪ We're gonna rock this town ♪
♪ Rock it inside out ♪
Ladies.
She's coming down.
And... showtime.
♪ Life's the same ♪
♪ I'm moving in stereo ♪
♪ Except for my shoes ♪
♪ Life's the same ♪
♪ You're shakin' like tremolo ♪
♪ It's all inside you ♪
Hey, lard-ass!
No running on my watch!
I gotta warn you again,
and you're banned for life.
You wanna be banned for life, lard-ass?
Didn't think so.
Afternoon, ladies.
Afternoon, Billy.
Dig the new suit, Mrs. Wheeler.
Thank you.
- Hey.
You busy?
You're our first customer, so...
What now?
And then El, she just... slams the door.
Right in my face.
Uh-huh?
You know, it is that smug
son of a bitch, Mike.
He's corrupting her, I'm telling you.
And I'm just gonna lose it.
I mean, I am gonna lose it, Joyce.
Just take it down, Hopper.
I need for them to break up.
That is not your decision.
They're spending entirely too much
time together.
You agree with me about that, right?
Well, I mean, they're just kissing, right?
Yeah, but it is constant.
It is constant.
Okay? That is not normal,
that is not healthy.
You can't just force them apart.
I mean,
they're not little kids anymore, Hop.
They're teenagers.
If you order them around like a cop,
then they're gonna rebel.
It's just what they do.
So what, I'm just supposed to
let them do whatever they want?
No, I didn't say that.
I think you should... talk to them.
No. No. 'Cause talking doesn't work.
Not yelling. Not ordering.
But talk to them.
You know, like a heart-to-heart.
A heart-to-heart?
What is that?
You sit them down and you talk to them,
like you're their friend.
I find if you talk to them
like you're on their level,
then they really start to listen.
And then, you know,
you could start to create some boundaries.
- Boundaries.
- Yeah, but,
Hop, it's really important
that no matter how they respond,
you stay calm.
You cannot lose your temper.
Uh...
Maybe you could do it for me?
No.
Yeah, you could. Yeah, you could.
You come over after work.
- Yes.
- No.
It only works if it comes from you.
But...
- But?
- Maybe I can help you...
find the right words.
♪ Ooh, whoa! ♪
♪ Some days won't end ever
And some days pass on by ♪
♪ I'll be workin' here forever... ♪
- Thanks, hon.
- For you.
For you.
- Thanks.
- Welcome.
Oh, no, no, no, no! Nancy!
Sorry.
- How 'bout a piece on Iran?
- I want something local.
I hear there's a beauty pageant
at the fair this year.
Yeah, I'm looking for above the fold here,
Bruce.
Then clearly you haven't seen
Lucy Lebrock,
because I'm not sure she'll fit
above the fold!
Fellas!
In six hours, we go to print.
I need something real.
Oh, I think they're real.
What about Starcourt?
I... I was just...
thinking...
I mean, I know everyone
loves the mall, but...
how many small businesses have closed
since it opened?
Like, five on Main, at least.
It's changing the fabric of our town
- in a way...
- "The Death of Small-Town America."
I like it.
I like it a lot.
But I think I've got something
even spicier.
It's about the missing mustard
on my hamburger.
You think you can follow the clues
and solve the case
of the missing condiment, Nancy Drew?
Sorry.
Look out, Phil,
she might be after your job!
Ow, ow, ow. Ow.
Better?
Still stings.
Is that a new zit?
What is wrong with you?
I was just asking!
I call it... the Forever Clock.
All right? Powered by wind.
Very useful in the apocalypse.
Then, I give you...
the Slammer.
Pretty neat, huh?
But this...
this is my masterpiece.
I would like you to meet...
Cerebro.
What exactly are we looking at here?
An unassembled one-of-a-kind
battery-powered radio tower.
So, it's a... a ham radio.
The Cadillac of ham radios.
This baby carries
a crystal-clear connection
over vast distances.
I'm talking North Pole to South.
I can talk to my girlfriend
whenever and wherever I choose.
Girlfriend?
Wait, so her name is Suzie?
Suzie with a "z." She's from Utah.
Girls go to science camp?
- Suzie does. She's a genius.
- Is she cute?
Think Phoebe Cates, only hotter.
- What's going on?
- Going to talk to Dustin's girlfriend.
Girlfriend?
Alrighty, one scoop of chocolate.
That's a buck-twenty-five.
Anything else?
Ooh, Purdue.
- Fancy.
- Yeah, I'm excited.
Yeah, you know, I considered it,
Purdue, but then I was like,
you know what?
I really think I need some real-life
experience, you know,
before I hit college,
see what it feels like.
Kinda like, uh, I don't know,
see what it's like to earn
a working-man's wage, you know? Uh...
Oh, I'm sorry.
- I think that's, like, really important.
- Yeah, totally.
Yeah, anyway, this was, like, so fun.
We should kind of like, you know,
I don't know,
maybe hang out this weekend or...
Oh, sorry about that. Uh...
I don't know. Maybe next weekend or...
Yeah, I'm busy.
Oh, that's cool. I'm...
I'm working here next weekend, so...
the following weekend's better for me.
No. I'm sorry, I can't.
Okay. Thanks.
I...
This is... my first day here.
And another one bites the dust.
You are oh-for-six, Popeye.
Yeah, yeah, I can count.
You know that means you suck.
Yep, I can read, too.
Since when?
It's this stupid hat.
I am telling you,
it is totally blowing my best feature.
Yeah, company policy is a real drag.
You know, it's a crazy idea,
but have you considered...
telling the truth?
Oh, you mean,
that I couldn't even get into Tech
and my douchebag dad's
trying to teach me a lesson,
I make three bucks an hour,
and I have no future? That truth?
Hey, twelve o'clock.
Oh, shit. Oh, shit. Okay... Uh...
I'm going in. Okay?
And you know what?
- Screw company policy.
- Oh, my God, you're a whole new man.
Right? Ooh.
Ahoy, ladies! Didn't see you there.
Would you guys like to set sail
on this ocean of flavor with me?
I'll be your captain.
I'm Steve Harrington.
Oh, God.
Can I get you guys a little taste
of the Cherries Jubilee?
No? Anybody?
Banana Boat? Four people, four spoons?
Share it in the booth?
Anybody? It's hot out there.
I know this is
a difficult conversation to have...
but I hope you know that I...
care about you very much.
- And I know that you...
- Eye contact.
And I know that you...
both care about each other very much.
This does not sound like me at all.
Just keep going. Come on.
Which is why I think it's important
to establish these boundaries...
moving forward...
No looking. You know this.
Come on.
...so we can build an environment...
uh...
where we...
all feel comfortable
and trusted
and open...
"Share our feelings..."
...to sharing our feelings...
This isn't gonna work.
Um, it's not gonna work.
It's not gonna work.
Yes, it will! I promise.
Oh, come on.
Maybe I'll just kill Mike.
I'm the chief of police,
I could cover it up.
You got this.
I promise.
♪ I really don't know what I know ♪
♪ It won't let... ♪
You wanna have dinner tonight?
You can give me some more pointers.
Oh, I... Um...
Um, I...
I have plans.
Okay, sure.
Oh, a customer.
- Hey, Carol!
- Oh, hi, Joyce!
How are you? So good to see you.
So, um, Georgie has
his 13th birthday coming up.
Oh, my gosh, 13?
I know!
And I'm a little lost...
♪ She's got you ♪
Aren't we high enough?
Cerebro works best at a hundred meters.
You know, I'm pretty sure people in Utah
have telephones.
Yeah, but Suzie's Mormon.
Oh, shit. She doesn't have electricity?
Oh, that's the Amish.
- What are Mormons?
- Super religious white people.
They have electricity and cars and stuff,
but...
since I'm not Mormon,
her parents would never approve.
It's all a bit...
Shakespearean.
Shakespearean?
Yeah. Like Romeo and Juliet.
Right.
- Star-crossed lovers.
- I got it.
Hey, guys!
This is fun and all, but, uh...
I have to go home.
- We're almost there.
- Sorry, man.
Curfew.
- Come on, let's go.
- Good luck.
- Curfew at 4:00?
- They're lying.
- It's been like this all summer.
- It's romantic.
- It's gross.
- It's bullshit.
I just got home.
Well, their loss, right?
Onwards and upwards!
Suzie awaits!
Will, come on!
♪ Well I'm ♪
♪ Hot blooded ♪
♪ Check it and see ♪
♪ I've got a fever ♪
♪ Of a hundred and three ♪
♪ Come on baby ♪
♪ Do you do more than dance? ♪
♪ I'm hot blooded, I'm hot blooded... ♪
Looking good out there, Mrs. Wheeler.
Thank you.
Perfect form.
Well...
your form is amazing.
I'm sorry, I mean, I...
I've seen you... uh, teaching...
...lessons. Swimming lessons.
You know, I could, uh...
I could teach you, if you like.
Oh.
I know all the styles.
Freestyle.
Butterfly.
Breaststroke.
- Oh.
- Oh!
You okay?
I didn't think you...
I didn't think you taught adults.
Well, I offer more, uh...
advanced lessons to select clientele.
Oh.
Come to think of it, there is a good pool
out at a Motel 6 on Cornwallis.
It's very quiet.
You know, very private.
Mm.
Shall we say tonight?
Eight o'clock?
I'm sorry.
I can't.
Can't what? Have fun?
- Mrs. Wheeler!
- No.
I... I... I just, uh...
I don't think I need any lessons.
Oh, you see, I think you do.
I just don't think
that you've had the right teacher.
- I, uh...
- It will be
the workout of your life.
Made it.
Yeah, only took five hours.
Why couldn't we just play D&D?
I'm so thirsty.
Did you seriously just drink
the rest of our water?
Pretty impressive, right?
- Yeah.
- Now, you ready to meet my love?
- Okay, sure.
- Yeah.
Suzie, this is Dustin. Do you copy? Over.
One sec. She's probably...
She's still there.
Suzie...
this is Dustin. Do you copy? Over.
I'm sure she's there. It's just...
- Yeah.
- You know, maybe she's, like, busy or...
- It's around dinnertime.
- Mmm.
- Yep.
Here.
Suzie, do you copy? This is Dustin. Over.
Hey, guys, I'm home.
Guys?
Hello?
Ah!
So, who do you wanna speak to next?
I'm talking about Frasier, Sam.
He had a couple of sips of Chianti tonight
and asked me to marry him.
Did you say a couple of sips,
or barrels?
Ahh!
- Ah, they're funny, don't you think?
- Yes.
I just wish they'd
get back together again already.
Me too.
You don't think that I still...
- Well, of course I...
- You bet your...
Tell everyone that I'll call
after the wedding tomorrow.
Tomorrow? What's the rush?
Frasi er has thoughtfully
and romantically
arranged for us to be married
at the Marino estate.
Shit, shit.
Hawkins Post.
Um, hold on, I'm...
I'm sorry, can you... can you repeat that?
♪...than I ever thought I might ♪
♪ And I can't fight this feeling
Anymore... ♪
...why it's important
to establish these boundaries...
moving forward, so that we can
create an environment where...
you feel comfortable and trusted
and open.
Shit.
"To share our feelings."
Hey.
Yes?
Can I talk to you guys a minute?
Hi.
♪ My life has been such a whirlwind
Since I saw you ♪
♪ I've been running around in circles
In my mind ♪
♪ And it always seems
That I'm following you, girl ♪
♪ 'Cause you take me to the places ♪
♪ That alone I'd never fi... ♪
Um...
What I, uh...
needed to say to you...
What I wanted
to say to you...
is that, um...
Uh-oh.
I think we're in trouble.
No.
No, nobody's in trouble, okay?
I just, um...
Uh...
You know what?
Your mom called.
What?
Yeah.
She needs you home right away.
Is everything okay?
No, I don't think so.
It's your grandma.
- Is she dead?
- No.
- Did she fall again?
Does she have cancer?
- No.
- Then I don't understand.
What's wrong with Nana?
Nothing! There's nothing wrong with Nana!
- What?
- But...
there's something very wrong
with this thing between you and El.
Oh, you lying piece of shit!
You're crazy!
Crazy?
You want to see real crazy?
You disrespect me again.
Okay?
Here's what's gonna happen.
I'm gonna drive you home.
And I'm gonna speak...
and you're going to listen.
And then, maybe...
maybe by the end of it,
maybe if you're lucky, maybe...
I will continue
to allow you to date my daughter.
Nod if you understand!
...do you copy? This is Dustin. Over.
Suzie! This is Dustin. Do you copy? Over.
Suzie, this is your Dustin.
Do you copy? Over.
- Suzie...
- Dustin, come on! She's not there.
She's there, all right? She'll pick up.
- Maybe Cerebro doesn't work.
- Or maybe Suzie doesn't exist.
She exists!
She's a genius
and she's hotter than Phoebe Cates?
No girl is that perfect.
Is that so?
I mean...
you're perfect.
I mean, like, per... perfect
in your own way.
In your special... your own special way.
Relax, I was teasing.
I'm obviously perfect
and Dustin's obviously lying.
Come on, Don Juan.
- Where are you going?
- Home.
Well... guess it's just you and me, Byers.
Um... it's late.
Sorry.
Maybe tomorrow we can play D&D.
Or something fun. Like we used to?
Yeah, sure.
Welcome home.
Yeah.
Shit.
Suzie? Suzie, is that you?
The silver cat feeds...
when blue meets yellow in the west...
A trip to China sounds nice...
If you tread lightly...
The week is long...
The silver cat feeds...
Beautiful,
isn't it?
♪ I keep looking for something
I can't get ♪
♪ Broken hearts lie all around me ♪
♪ And I don't see an easy way
To get out of this ♪
♪ Her diary sits by the bedside table ♪
♪ The curtains are closed
The cat's in the cradle ♪
♪ Who would've thought
That a boy like me ♪
♪ Could come to this? ♪
♪ Oh, oh, I ♪
♪ I just died in your arms tonight ♪
♪ It must've been something you said ♪
♪ It must've been some kind of kiss ♪
♪ I should've walked away ♪
Hey, Karen.
You don't mind if I call you Karen,
do you?
Good.
Oh, no.
No. Piece of shit.
Shit.
Damn it!
Ah, shit.
Piece of shit!
What the hell?
Who's there?
Hey!
I said, who's there?